

PERSONALITY

SKILLS

EDITTING

WEB DESIGN

1. SD DON BOSCO

2. SMP DON BOSCO

3. SMA DON BOSCO

PROGRAMMING

GRAPHIC DESIGN

EDUCATION

4. UNIVERSITAS TARUMANGARA

RESPONSIBLE

COMMUNICATIVE

ABLE TO TEAMWORK

DISCIPLINE & HONESTY

CURRICULUM VITAE

GEORGE WEILIS JUNIOR

IPK 3.96 / 4.00

ABOUT ME

My name is George Weilis Junior, I am a student at Tarumanagara University majoring in Information Technology. I have quite a lot of experience in the IT field, and have knowledge about Creative Design. I understand how to use Photoshop, Premier Pro, Illustrator, FL Studio for Design, and understand programming languages such as Python, C++, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and many others. I want to and willing to learn new programming languages as to expand my knowledge.

DATA PERSONAL

: George Weilis Junior

Place and Date of Birth : Jakarta, February 20, 2003

SEX : Male

Religion : Catholic

Education : College Student

Nationality : Indonesia

Address : Puspa Gading 7, Penggangsaan Dua,

Kelapa Gading, Jakarta Utara

ORGANIZATION

1. Committee in OSIS on Highschool

ACHIEVEMENT

1. Second place in CORISINDO 2024 Game Development in UTB

EXPERIENCE

- 1. NEXT!!! Game Development Game developed using Unity engine and C#
- 2. Worldle

Mobile game application that uses Flutter Android Manager as the engine, Firebase for the database and the uses of other various help such as Jira and Figma

3. Wizdrawal

E-Money team-code application that uses Flutter and Firebase mainly

4. Retro Hardware Store Website that uses EJS, CSS, JavaScript, MongoDB to promote various retro device

CONTACT ME

Georgeweiliz21@gmail.com George, 535220173@stu.untar.ac.id

2008 - 2014

2014 - 2017 2017 - 2020

2022 - 2024



0851-7975-6235 / WA

